/*---------------------------Questions for Intermediate Level------------------------*/
/*-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------*/
window.gameIntermediateLevelQuestions = [
    {
        question: "2 > 3",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "-4 < -3",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: "Yes",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "2.55 < 2.558",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: 16,
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "2/5 > 3/5",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "8.012 < 8.002",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "12/18 < 13/18",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: "Yes",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "0.001 > 0.01",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "1.00012 < 1.00120",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: "Yes",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "100000 < 99999",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "12.04 > 144/12",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: "Yes",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "-12.89 > -12.88",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "625/25 > 25",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "32/8 > 4",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "-3.9998 > -3.9999",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "Yes",
        correctAnswer: "Yes",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "4.9999 < 4.9998",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "121*11 > 1333",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "42/7 < 5.95",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "5/2 > 2.6",
        answerArray: ["Yes", "No"],
        matchedValue: "No",
        correctAnswer: "No",
        isVisited: 0
    }
];
